[
  {
    "Front": "σάρξ",
    "Back": " sb. 3 f.: kød"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σαφής",
    "Back": " adj. 3: tydelig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σελήνη",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: måne"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σηµαίνω",
    "Back": " vb.: viser"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σηµεῖον",
    "Back": " sb. 2 n.: tegn"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σθένος",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n.: styrke"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σιγάω",
    "Back": " vb.: tier"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σιγή",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: tavshed"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σίδηρος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: jern"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σῖτος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: korn, mad"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σκέπτοµαι",
    "Back": " vb.: ser på"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σκευάζω",
    "Back": " vb.: skaffer udstyr"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σκεῦος",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n.: udstyr"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σκέψις",
    "Back": " sb. 3 f.: undersøgelse"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σκοπέω",
    "Back": " vb.: sigter, spejder"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σκοπός",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: mål (at sigte efter)"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σοφία",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: visdom"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σοφιστής",
    "Back": " sb. 1 m.: vismand"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σοφός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: klog"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σπείρω",
    "Back": " vb.: sår, spreder"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σπέρµα",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n.: sæd"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σπεύδω",
    "Back": " vb.: iler"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σπορά",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: såning"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σπουδάζω",
    "Back": " vb.: er alvorlig"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σπουδαῖος",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: seriøs"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σπουδή",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: alvor"
  },
  {
    "Front": "στέλλω",
    "Back": " vb.: sender"
  },
  {
    "Front": "στερέω",
    "Back": " vb.: berøver"
  },
  {
    "Front": "στέφανος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: krans"
  },
  {
    "Front": "στόλος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: udsendt gruppe"
  },
  {
    "Front": "στόµα",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n.: mund"
  },
  {
    "Front": "στρατεία",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: krigstogt"
  },
  {
    "Front": "στρατεύω",
    "Back": " vb.: er i felten"
  },
  {
    "Front": "στρατηγός",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: militær leder"
  },
  {
    "Front": "στρατιά",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: krigstogt"
  },
  {
    "Front": "στρατιώτης",
    "Back": " sb. 1 m.: soldat"
  },
  {
    "Front": "στρατόπεδον",
    "Back": " sb. 2 n.: militær lejr"
  },
  {
    "Front": "στρατός",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: hær"
  },
  {
    "Front": "στρέφω",
    "Back": " vb.: vender"
  },
  {
    "Front": "στροφή",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: drejning"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σύ",
    "Back": " pron.: du"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σύµµαχος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: forbundsfælle"
  },
  {
    "Front": "συµφορά",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: tilfælde"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σύν",
    "Back": " præp. m. dat.: (sammen) med"
  },
  {
    "Front": "συχνός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: tætpakket"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σφόδρα",
    "Back": " adv.: voldsomt"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σχεδόν",
    "Back": " adv.: næsten"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σχῆµα",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n.: stilling"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σχολή",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: ro"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σῴζω",
    "Back": " vb.: redder"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σῶµα",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n.: krop"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σωτήρ",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: redningsmand"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σωτηρία",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: redning"
  },
  {
    "Front": "σώφρων",
    "Back": " adj. 3 m./f.: klog, forsigtig"
  }
]